Lee Yunseo!
Are you okay? Please answer me!
What happened?
Or should I call the kids?
I'll go and see
If I don't hear from you within 5 minutes
call the kids
Okay
Yunseo Lee
Where are you?
Answer me!
Lee Yunseo!
Because there are six of us
Just pick two more people and it's over.
Hey, what should I do?
What should I do?
Park Woo-ram, this bastard
I'm going to show them what the mafia is like.
let's go
Still, the remaining people
I'm glad it's you two.
Do it quickly
Uh, I'll do it now.
I hate it
Don't force it
Huh?
Jisoo
This is me
I'm never forcing it
We're in a bad situation right now...
Please change your position and think about it.
If it's not you now, it's Go Kyung-jun
But now you are doing this
Are you feeling pressured to even think about it properly?
What's wrong
you
No way
You think I'm a mafia?
You don't know that
Would you mind going out so we can think about it among ourselves?
fuck
Hey Wooram!
Uram-ah
They told me
How can you do this? uh?
Fuck, really
Jisoo too
It must be because it was so sudden.
I'll tell you well
So first
Stay in your room, okay?
Hello, hello!
It's our school
Huh?
fuck
Hey, Choi Mina!
Park Woo-ram Where is this bastard?
on the 4th floor
Hey, just sleep.
Park Woo-ram, are you with the kids?
no
The kids are talking on the third floor
You're in the same boat as us.
Let's row together
What are you talking about?
Bring me a mafia bastard
Huh?
Then Jisoo you
Think about it some more
Yujun
Quickly pick Go Kyung-jun first.
Uh, okay.
Don't force it?
I'll take some time to think
No, don't think about it.
What else is there?
It's not anyone else, it's Wooram
Why?
Honestly, she always cursed at Jooyoung.
That's it.
Wooram is our friend, huh?
Yes, Jisoo
Let’s take Wooram’s side.
Cha Yu-jun, come to your senses.
Find the mafia
I'm not going home, really!
I don't trust anyone, even if I'm a friend or something.
And he was probably pushed by Donghyun.
how do you know
Hey, what did you just say?
Stop it
It's not time for us to fight among ourselves
Jisoo Park, I need to see it again
Wow, how can I live alone?
And Yujun has no sense of purpose either.
Uram-ah
Wooram Park
Don't you have any?
Where is Wooram?
I told you to stay in your room
Let's find out
Yujun is alone?
Uh, well, because of voting.
Where there is no index
I want to talk to you...
Hey, hey, Cha Yu-jun
Icy, hey, move it, move it
Just take a little more time
I'll show you how to catch the mafia
Ah, Mr.
Hey Wooram
Wooram Park
Hey, Park Woo-ram
Hey Wooram
Not here either
That doesn't work, let's find it separately.
uh
Park Woo-ram!
Hey Wooram!
Tell me, fuck
Ah, this bastard!
Speak!
Ha, don't do it
Please, please
Fuck you bastard
How dare you kill me, fuck
Hey
Wooram Park
I think he passed out?
Hey, hey
Maybe you can pretend
Jisoo
It's past 11 o'clock and you're not voting?
Let’s just film Go Kyung-jun, okay?
Hey, hey, wait a minute
No, I said I need time to think about it.
Why are you rushing again?
You only have to vote before twelve o'clock.
Think about it a little more
Park Woo-ram!
uh?
Hey Wooram
Park Woo-ram!
Garden,
What about Yunseo?
I don't know, I don't know
I got to the end but it was blocked.
It's blocked?
uh
I guess I'll have to go out and look for it.
Jeong-won Oh, Jeong-won Oh!
why?
Yoon Seo-ya
Yoonseo, you were worried.
- Are you okay?
- Uh
I fell into the basement
There was a room with CCTV.
But I went out
It suddenly changed to the second floor.
I really
Even after going around for a while
Just come out to the same place
I barely got out
I fell into the basement
Why is it on the 2nd floor?
and in there
Everything was blocked
really
I found this too
Is it our school?
He seems like a senior at our school
I don't know
No, but why is your face like this?
I feel bad
This person
Looks like the ghost I saw
Huh?
Yoon Seo-ya
Is Wooram here?
- No
- I said I would go to my room.
It suddenly disappeared
No time, hurry up
No time! You fucking bastard
Look at how vicious this bastard is.
This bastard is a mafia?
catch
Get it!
하지 마
하지 마, 씨발 새끼야, 하지 마
뭘 하지 마?
I haven't even started yet
Ha, don't do it! Don't do it
Anyway, you bastard
I really don't like the color of your eyes
How should I dig it?
So fuck it, it's going to be fine
Why do you touch people?
Uram-ah
Hey Wooram!
Hey, Park Woo-ram!
Isn’t it on the second floor too?
There is no
It's not on the first floor or in the basement.
Shall we go to the annex?
I'm Park Woo-ram.
What is it?
I'm a mafia
I killed Jooyoung Lee
What is it, Park Woo-ram?
What is this?
broadcasting room
Me too, like that
It's not like I really liked it.
I'm so pissed because I gave it to you.
Because you ignore people
That's why I wanted to fucking kill you
Damn you crazy bastard
Park Woo-ram?
What does he say?
They say they are the mafia
Are you done?
Is that okay, you fucking bastard!
Fuck you bastard
It will blow a long time ago
Hey Wooram! Hey, Park Woo-ram!
hey!
Hey, hey, Go Gyeongjun!
hey! Open the door!
Hey guys
Guys, I'm here!
hey! Mr.
Hey!
Oh, give it to me
It's all out
Fuck you, Kim Jun-hee!
You crazy bastards!
Mr.
You guys are crazy, you guys are crazy!
are you okay? Ha, Mr.
Fuck, who's really crazy?
This bastard mafia
You bastard who killed Jooyoung Lee!
Don't be a dick, Mr.
Come to your senses, you idiot.
Look
It's all over
Fuck!
Go Kyung-jun, that bastard first
I should have killed him
I was just a fucking asshole, huh?
씨발
야, 야, 야, 야
우람아
같이 가자, 이 개새끼야!
hey!
Hey, be careful.
You crazy bastard!
Do something with that bastard!
i fuck
I'm going to kill you!
어차피 넌 나 아니라도
딴 마피아한테 뒤졌어
일로 와, 이 씨발 새끼야
죽어!
voting
It has ended
The person with the most votes was Park Woo-ram.
will be executed
Park Woo-ram's occupation is mafia.
See, I'm right.
- Come out! Mr.
- Aren't you going in?
Take care of Yunseo